http://www.fuelcelltoday.com/privacy_policy

This website uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Find out more about cookies
RSS Feeds
You are here:
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Johnson Matthey respects your privacy and is committed toprotecting your personal information.Please read this Privacy Notice carefully as it containsimportant information on how and why Johnson Matthey collects and processesyour personal information through your use of this website, and on your rightsin relation to your personal information.Who are we?Johnson Matthey is made up of different legal entities. ThisPrivacy Notice is issued on behalf of the Johnson Matthey Group. References to“Johnson Matthey”, “we”, “us” or “our” relate to the relevant company in theJohnson Matthey Group responsible for processing your personal information.For the purposes of applicable data protection laws (includingthe EUGeneral Data Protection Regulation, “GDPR”) Johnson MattheyPlc (with company number 00033774 and registered office at 5th Floor, 25Farringdon Street, London, EC4A 4AB) is the controller of your personalinformation and responsible for this website, www.matthey.com.Our contact details are provided in the contact section below.What information do we collect about you?“Personal information” means information that enables you to beidentified, either directly or indirectly.We may collect, use, store or transfer some or all the followingkinds of personal information about you: Behavioural information
on your visit to the website: As you interact with our
website, we automatically collect technical data about your equipment,
browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data using
cookies. Please see our cookies notice for further
information regarding our use of cookies. Email address, where you have
requested receipt of a regular email communication. Contact
information,
including your full name, company name, telephone number and email
address, where you have submitted an enquiry via our website contact
forms.We do not collect any sensitive information about you (such asdetails about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sexlife, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership,information about your health or genetic and biometric data) or any informationregarding criminal convictions or offences.Why, and on what basis, do we use your personal information?Data protection laws require that we have a legal basis on whichto process your personal information.To fulfil our legitimate interestsIt is in our legitimate interests to give users of our websitethe best possible and most secure experience. We therefore use the personalinformation we collect about you to tailor and improve our website experiencefor users, send you email messages relevant to your stated interest(s), andrespond to any direct enquiries you submit via our website contact forms.We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you(both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personalinformation for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personalinformation for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact onyou (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to bylaw).To comply with our contractual and/or legal obligationsThere may be other grounds on which we process your personalinformation. Processing may be necessary for the performance of a contract wehave with you, or for us to comply with our legal obligations.Who do we share your personal information with?We may share your personal information with the followingparties where it is necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for: Associated entities
within the Johnson Matthey Group External
third parties,
including:
Service providers
(acting as data processors) who provide IT and system administration
services Law
enforcement or other authorities where required to do so to comply with a
legal or regulatory obligation. We require all third parties to respect the security of yourpersonal information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do notallow our third party service providers to use your personal information fortheir own purposes and only permit them to process your personal informationfor specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.International transfersYour personal information may be transferred to, and stored at,a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) (for example, inthe USA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who workfor one of our service providers. We will take reasonable steps to ensure thatyour personal information is kept secure and treated in accordance with thisPrivacy Notice and applicable data protection laws, including, where relevant,by entering into appropriate contractual terms with the receiving party outsidethe EEA.How do we keep your personal information secure?We have put in place appropriate security measures to preventyour personal information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in anunauthorised way, altered or disclosed. We limit access to your personalinformation to those individuals who have a business need to access it. As partof our security measures, we may sometimes require you to give proof of youridentity before we disclose personal information to you.We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilitiesand attacks and carry out tests to identify ways to further strengthensecurity. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected datasecurity breach where we are legally required to do so.Third party linksOur website may include links to third-party websites, plug-insand applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections mayallow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control thesethird-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. Whenyou leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every websiteyou visit.How long do we keep hold of your personal information?We will only retain your personal information for as long asnecessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for thepurposes of satisfying any legal, accounting or reporting requirements.Your rightsUnder the GDPR you have some important rights, which you canexercise free of charge. You have the right to: request details or
copies of the personal information we hold about you; request to have your
personal information corrected if it is inaccurate, and completed if it is
incomplete; in certain
circumstances, object to or restrict the processing of your personal
information; in certain
circumstances, request to have your personal information deleted or removed;
and in
certain circumstances, request to have your personal information
transferred to a third party.For further information on each of these rights, including thecircumstances in which they apply, see the guidance on individual rights fromthe UKInformation Commissioner’s Office or contact us (seecontact section below).Job applicantsWhen you apply for a job with us (whether you already work forJohnson Matthey or not), we will collect, store and use personal informationabout you, including information provided in a CV, application form or coverletter, information provided to us during interviews and assessments, recordsof qualifications, skills and training, references, copies of right to workdocumentation, and records of pre-employment checks. Some of the information wecollect about you may be more sensitive, such as information about your race orethnic origin, health, and any previous criminal convictions/offences.We collect this recruitment information direct from you duringthe recruitment process and from third parties, including former employers,employment agencies and background check providers.We use the recruitment information we collect to: assess your skills,
qualifications, and suitability for the work/role; carry out background and
reference checks, where applicable and where permitted by local laws; communicate with you
about the recruitment process;
decide whether to enter
into a contract of employment (or other service) with you; keep records relating to
our hiring processes; and comply with legal or
regulatory requirements.Subject to local laws, we may retain recruitment information forup to two years after we have communicated to you our decision about whether toappoint you to the role. We may retain your personal information for thatperiod so that we can show, in the event of a legal claim, that we have notdiscriminated against candidates on prohibited grounds and that we haveconducted the recruitment exercise in a fair and transparent way. Changes to this Privacy NoticeWe may update this privacy notice from time to time in responseto changing legal, regulatory or operational requirements. We will notify youof any material changes via a pop-up notice on the website.This privacy notice was last updated on: 24 May 2018.ContactIf you have any questions or concerns about the way we treatyour personal information, any questions about your rights in relation to yourinformation, or if you would like to request a copy of the personal informationwe hold about you, please contact us at:Address:Head of Data ProtectionJohnson Matthey Plc5th Floor, 25 Farringdon StreetLondonEC4A 4ABTel: +44 20 7269 8400Email: DPO@matthey.comWebsite: www.matthey.comMaking a complaintPlease contact us in thefirst instance so that we can try to address any concerns you have directly.Should you wish to escalate your concerns, you have the right tolodge a complaint with your local Data Protection Authority. The name andcontact details of the Data Protection Authorities in the European Union can beaccessed here.
Useful Links
Terms & Conditions
Sitemap
Privacy
Cookies
Tools
Print
Twitter
